const arithmetic_firstterm = [
    {
      question: "If the 10th term is 46 and the common difference is 5, what is the first term?",
      options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "If the 12th term is 35 and d = 3, find the first term.",
      options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "The 20th term is 95 and d = 5. Find the first term.",
      options: ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "If a₁₅ = 70 and d = 4, what is a₁?",
      options: ["8", "9", "10", "11"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "The 25th term is 100 and d = 4. Find a₁.",
      options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
      answer: 0
    },
    {
      question: "If a₈ = 50 and d = 7, what is a₁?",
      options: ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "The 30th term is 200 and d = 7. Find the first term.",
      options: ["-4", "-5", "-6", "-7"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "If the 18th term is 85 and d = 5, what is the first term?",
      options: ["-2", "-3", "-4", "-5"],
      answer: 0
    },
    {
      question: "The 50th term is 150 and d = 3. Find a₁.",
      options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "If a₁₂ = 92 and d = 8, what is a₁?",
      options: ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "The 40th term is 100 and d = 2. Find a₁.",
      options: ["20", "21", "22", "23"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "If the 15th term is 200 and d = 15, find a₁.",
      options: ["-20", "-25", "-30", "-35"],
      answer: 0
    },
    {
      question: "The 60th term is 500 and d = 9. Find a₁.",
      options: ["-31", "-32", "-33", "-34"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "If a₂₀ = 145 and d = 8, what is the first term?",
      options: ["-10", "-11", "-12", "-13"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "The 25th term is 210 and d = 10. Find a₁.",
      options: ["-30", "-35", "-40", "-45"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "If a₁₀ = 400 and d = 50, what is the first term?",
      options: ["-50", "-60", "-70", "-80"],
      answer: 0
    },
    {
      question: "The 100th term is 1000 and d = 11. Find a₁.",
      options: ["-88", "-89", "-90", "-91"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      question: "If a₁₅ = 320 and d = 20, find a₁.",
      options: ["25", "30", "35", "40"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      question: "The 50th term is 350 and d = 7. Find a₁.",
      options: ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
      answer: 0
    },
    {
      question: "If a₁₈ = 200 and d = 12, what is a₁?",
      options: ["-10", "-11", "-12", "-13"],
      answer: 2
    }
  ];
  